For my first attempt, I took the problem at face value and thought,
第一次尝试时 我考虑的是问题表面 我想的是
what if all I cared about was a tickets priority level and nothing else.
如果我唯一关心的是罚款单的优先级 其他都不考虑呢
And in that case, I could just have three bags.
在这种情况下 我只需要三个袋子
And after filling out each ticket,
在填写好每张罚款单后
I would just toss it in the appropriate bag.
就将其放进一个合适的袋子里
Whether it's high, low, or medium priority.
无论其优先级为高、低或中
And this really isn't a terrible solution.
这个方案真的谈不上糟糕
In fact, it's a great solution if the tickets priority
实际上 如果罚款单优先级的确是我们所关心的数据中的
really is the only structure in the data that we care about.
唯一结构 这个方案非常棒
But, it's probably not.
不过 实际情况并非如此
We probably do care about when a ticket was filed as well.
我们可能同样关心罚款单何时能归档
And that thinking, I made option two,
根据这种思维 我制作了第二种方案
which is to sort by priority on insert.
那就是插入时通过优先级分类
And in this option we go back to having a box.
在这种方案中 我们假设有一个盒子
But now the goal is to make sure that these tickets stay
不过 现在的目标是确保这些罚款单
sorted first by priority, and then by date.
首先通过优先级分类 然后再通过日期分类
So all the high priority tickets,
因此 所有高优先级的罚款单
would be in the back.
都会在后面
All the tickets in the middle,
所有放在中间的罚款单
would be medium priority,
都是中优先级的
and all the tickets at the front would be low priority.
而所有在前面的罚款单都是低优先级的
Now, let's think about how I would have to use this system.
现在 让我们想想如何使用这个系统
In this system when I go to file a high priority ticket for example,
例如 在这个系统中 当我归档高优先级罚款单时
I'm first going to have to find where it belongs.
我首先必须找到罚款单的归属地方
So, in this example, I would need to search through all of these tickets that
在本例中 我需要搜寻所有已经放在盒子中的罚款单
are already in the box until I find the first high priority ticket,
直到找到第一张优先级最高的罚款单
and that's where I would have to put this one,
这就是我将放这张罚款单的地方
right in front of the first type priority ticket.
在第一类优先级的罚款单前面
And initially I did really like the solution,
一开始 我真的很喜欢这种方案
but this extra time required to file a ticket started bothering me.
不过归档罚款单需要额外的时间 这让我觉得麻烦
When I'm in the vehicle, I should be focused on the vehicle not on filing my tickets.
当我在车辆中时 我需要专注于车辆 而不是归档罚款单
So when I do file tickets,
因此 当我归档罚款单时
that process really ought to be as fast as possible.
速度应该越快越好
And this led me to the third option and the one I ended up taking,
这让我想到了第三种方案 也是我最终选择的方案
which is to have multiple boxes.
采用多个盒子
And in this option I just replaced my one box of tickets with three.
在这种方案中 我只是将罚款单的盒子从一个换成了三个
One for each of the priorities. So here I have a low priority box,
每个盒子代表一种优先级 这里是优先级为低的盒子
a medium priority box,
这里是优先级为中的盒子
and a high priority box.
这里是优先级较为高的盒子
And just to keep everything tidy,
为了保证一切井然有序
I keep all three of these in a little box itself.
我将这三个盒子放在了一个小盒子中
And then now, when I want to file a ticket,
然后 当我想要归档罚款单时
I just put it at the front of the appropriate box.
我只需把它插入合适的盒子中的前方
No rifling through all tickets required.
不用搜寻所有罚款单